Anna Topping

itsannatopping@gmail.com

603-533-0908

Senior Support Engineer

Works well with others. Experienced in web development, account management and problem solving.

Hardworking, responsible engineer with five years of client and project management experience.

Seeking opportunity to become an expert in a new platform and have impact through collaboration, teaching and problem solving.

Experience

Ungork I New York, NY

Senior Support Engineer I July 2021 - Present

I specialize in providing advanced technical support to Unqork creators, users, and engineers. This includes managing escalations with high profile clients such as Blackrock, Goldman Sachs, Liberty Mutual, and CoinBase. I am an expert in technical troubleshooting and providing step by step guidance to resolve complex configuration and platform issues. I work closely with the team leads to onboard new hires and clients using a custom curriculum and structure of my own creation.

Configuration Support Engineer | January 2021 - July 2021

I work closely with engineers, client partners, and delivery team to support Unqork built applications through the SDLC cycle. I am an expert in Unqork configuration through both my own research as well as hands on experience creating Unqork built tools for internal and external use. I share my knowledge with my teammates and those outside of the team who seek our guidance

Associate Support Engineer | April 2020 - January 2021

I use my exceptional problem solving and strong interpersonal communication skills to work with customers and to help resolve their complex Unqork problems.

Zero-In I New York, NY

Web Project Manager I January 2020 - April 2020

I work directly with developers to create new digital marketing solutions and manage API connections to business management softwares like MindBody, as well as integrations with social media platforms like Instagram, and Facebook. I manage the entire life of multiple high-profile web-based projects by communicating with clients, designers, and front end developers.

Digital Account Manager I September 2018 - December 2019

Manager of 73 mid-size accounts, I lead weekly project-update meetings, assess new content requests, and placate support issues and installation requests. I am an account manager as much as I am a project manager, overseeing the workflow for multiple projects at a time by organizing requirements, timelines, and scope. I work directly with clients to onboard users to CMS systems and provide excellent customer service with frequent reach outs and check-in video calls.

Education

General Assembly I New York, NY

Javascript Development I Jan 2020 - April 2020

Mastered the fundamentals of JavaScript and advanced APIs to build a full-functional mobile application.

Emmanuel College I Boston, MA I Class of 2017

Bachelor of Arts in English, Communications, and Media Studies. I GPA: 3.5

- Weekly volunteer with the Urban Food Project and Rosie's Place, 2016 Summer Community Service Fellow with Emmanuel's Food Project.
- Completed 3 internships with local businesses including WGBH's Direct Marketing Department.